BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.5224: National Master Freight Agreement and New England Area Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Employees of Private Common, Contract and Local Cartage Carriers, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Code no.5225: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - New York State Teamsters Joint Council Freight Division, Over-the-Road Motor Freight Agreement, 1958-1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Code no.5226: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - New York State Teamsters Joint Council Freight Division, Local Cartage Agreement, 1958-1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Code no.5227: National Master Freight Agreement and Virginia Freight Council, City Pickup and Delivery Cartage Agreement, 1961- 1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Code no.5229: National Master Freight Agreement and Maryland-District of Columbia Freight Council of the Eastern Conference of Teamsters, City Cartage Agreement, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Code no.5230: Motor Transport Labor Relations, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Code no.5231: Oregon Draymen and Warehousemen's Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 162, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Code no.5232: National Master Freight Agreement and Southeastern Area Over-the-Road Agreement, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Code no.5233: National Master Freight Agreement and Southeastern Area, Local Cartage, covering employees of Private, Common, Contract, and Local Cartage Carriers, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Code no.5234: National Master Freight Agreement and Southern Conference Local Freight Forwarding Office Clerical Employees Agreement, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Code no.5235: National Master Freight Agreement and Southern Conference Garage Agreement, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Code no.5236: National Master Freight Agreement and Southwestern Area, Over-the-Road Agreement, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Code no.5237: National Master Freight Agreement and Southwestern Area, Local Cartage, Covering employees of Private, Common, Contract, and Local Cartage Carriers, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Code no.5241: National Master Freight Agreement and Western States Area, Over-the-Road Single Man and Sleeper Cab Agreement, covering employees of Private, Common, and Contract Carriers, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Code no.5242: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 40, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Code no.5243: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 40, 1961-1970 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Code no.5245: California Trucking Association, Inc. and Agricultural and Horticultural Transportation, Locals 70, 85, 87, 94, 137, 150, 287, 315, 381, 386, 431, 439, 490, 533, 624, 684, 890, 912, 980, 1955-1958 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Code no.5247: National Master Freight Agreement and Western States Master Maintenance Trucking Agreement, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Code no.5250: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Express and General Trucking Agreement, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Code no.5251: National Master Freight Agreement and Philadelphia, PA and Vicinity Local Cartage and Over-the-Road Agreement, 1970- 1973 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Code no.5253: Milk Hauling Companies, New York and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 65, 182, 294, 316, 317, 445, 506, 529, 645, 648, 649, 680, 687, 693, 787, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Code no.5254: Eastern Labor Advisory Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 107, 311, 312, 384, 429, 470, 676, 773, 776, 866, 1963-1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Code no.5256: New Jersey-New York General Trucking Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 478, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Code no.5257: Express and General Trucking Agreement, New York and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 816, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Code no.5258: New Jersey-New York General Trucking Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 707, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Code no.5259: Northern New Jersey Area General Trucking Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 37, 469, 560, 617, 641, 660, 863, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Code no.5261: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Eastern Conference Area Milk Tank Haul Council, 1962-1970 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Code no.5262: National Master Freight Agreement and National Iron and Steel and Special Commodity Agreement, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Code no.5264: National Master Freight Agreement and Western States Area Pick-Up and Delivery Local Cartage and Dock Workers, 1964- 1970 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Code no.5265: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Western Master Freight Division, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Code no.5266: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Automotive Shop and Truck Servicing, Western Master Freight Division, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Code no.5267: California Trucking Association, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Western Master Freight Division, Locals 85, 87, 94, 104, 137, 150, 186, 224, 235, 287, 310, 315, 381, 386, 4, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Code no.5269: Private Carriers of Property by Motor Vehicle and Chicago Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and Vicinity (Independent), 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Code no.5270: Bowman Transportation Inc. and United Mine Workers of America Local 13600, International Union of District 50, 1967- 1970 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Code no.5274: Master Rail-Truck Freight Agreement and Southwest Area Road, City, Garage and Clerical Employees, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Code no.5400: Tanker Vessels throughout the United States and Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, District No. 1, 1965- 1969 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Code no.5203: No Employer and Highway Drivers, Dockmen, Spotters, Rampmen, Meat, Packing House and Allied Products Drivers and Helpers, Office Workers and Miscellaneous Employees, Local 710, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Code no.5221: Central Motor Freight Association, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 710, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Code no.591436: McCabe, Hamilton, and Renny Co., Limited and International Longshore and Warehousemen's Union Local 142, 1963- 1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Code no.561614: Connecticut Co. and Amalgamated Transit Union, Divisions 281, 425, 443, 1965-1973 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Code no.5022: Transport of New Jersey and Amalgamated Transit Union, Divisions 819, 820, 821, 822, 823, 824, 825, 880, 1972- 1974 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Series XII: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.6300: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 87, 235, 467, 542, 848, 871, and 982, 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Code no.6300: No Employer and Wholesale Delivery Drivers and Salesmen's Union, Local 848, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Code no.6302: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Food, Drug, and Beverage Warehousemen and Clerical Employees' Union, Local 595, 1958- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Code no.6306: San Francisco Employers Council and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 860, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Code no.6309: Distributor's Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 117, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Code no.6310: Distributor's Association and International Longshore and Warehouse Union Local 6 and 7, Warehouse Union Locals, 1961- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Code no.6318: International Harvester Co. and United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Locals 1152, 472, 688, 969, 119, 1004, 1115, 763, 710, 1004, 763, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Code no.6321: Tree Fruits Labor Relations Committee, Inc. and Fruit and Vegetable Packers and Warehousemen's Union, Local 760, 1970- 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Code no.260: Dried Fruit Industry and Packing House Employees and Warehousemen's Union, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Code no.5246: Los Angeles Warehousemen's Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 598, 1958-1961 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Code no.5255: United Parcel Service, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 22, 29, 171, 175, 322, 355, 453, 505, 539, 639, 697, 789, 822, 876, 992, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Code no.5271: United Parcel Service, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 705, 782, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Code no.5271: United Parcel Service, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 705, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Code no.5500: United States Post Office Dept. and National Association of Letter Carriers, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Code no.5500: United States Post Office Dept. and National Association of Post Office and General Services Maintenance Employees, 1963- 1970 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Code no.5500: United States Post Office Dept. and National Association of Special Delivery Messengers, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Code no.5500: United States Post Office Dept. and National Federation of Post Office Motor Vehicle Employees, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Code no.5500: United States Post Office Dept. and National Rural Letter Carriers Association, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Code no.5500: United States Post Office Dept. and United Federation of Postal Clerks, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Series XIII: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no.7904: The Associated Press and American Newspaper Guild Local 222, Wire Service Guild, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Code no.7911: No Employer and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 174, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Code no.560382: Several Employers and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 724, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Code no.7955: No Employer and International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Code no.7983: Walt Disney Productions and International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, and Motion Picture Screen Cartoonists, Local 839, 1965-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Code no.5701: Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania (Accounting Dept.), 1952- 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Code no.5702: Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and Pennsylvania Telephone Guild, 1944-1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Code no.5703: Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Code no.5705: Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1944, Pennsylvania Telephone Union, 1961-1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Code no.5707: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Code no.5711: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Maryland and Maryland Telephone Union, Inc., 1966-1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Code no.5713: General Telephone Company of Michigan and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Locals 818, 1172, 1174, 1177, 1190, 1410 - System Council T-3, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Code no.5715: General Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 1635, 1636, 1637, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Code no.5717: General Telephone Company of Indiana and Communications Workers of America, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Code no.5719: General Telephone Company of the Southwest and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Code no.5720: General Telephone Company of Ohio and Communications Workers of America, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Code no.5721: General Telephone Company of California and Communications Workers of America, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Code no.5722: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Code no.5724: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and Telephone Commercial Employees' Union, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Code no.5725: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and Commercial Telephone Workers' Union, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Code no.5726: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Code no.5731: Michigan Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Code no.5736: New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and New England Federation of Telephone Traffic Workers, 1968- 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Code no.5738: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Department and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Code no.5739: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 827, Telephone Workers Union, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Code no.5732: Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Plant Department and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Code no.5733: Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Department and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Code no.5742: Northwestern Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Code no.5744: New York Telephone Company and Telephone Commercial Union, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Code no.5750: Ohio Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Code no.5757: Pacific Telephone-Northwest (Washington-Idaho Area-Plant) and Communications Workers of America, 1960-1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Code no.5758: Pacific Telephone-Northwest (Washington-Idaho Area-Traffic) and Communications Workers of America, 1960-1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Code no.5760: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company, Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and Organization of Plant Clerical and Office Forces of Northern California and Nevada, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Code no.5761: Rochester Telephone Corporation and Communications Workers of America, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Code no.5762: Rochester Telephone Corporation and Rochester Telephone Workers Association, 1960-1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Code no.5765: Southwestern Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Code no.5773: Wisconsin Telephone Co. and Communications Workers of America of Wisconsin, Plant Department, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Code no.5774: Wisconsin Telephone Co. and Communications Workers of America, Traffic Department, 1966-1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Code no.5777: Western Union Telegraph Company and American Communications Association, 1958-1966 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Code no.5778: Western Union Telegraph Company and Commercial Telephone Workers' Union, 1958-1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Code no.5780: Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1961-1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Code no.5781: Several Employers and American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Code no.5791: General Telephone Company of Illinois and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 51 and 702, 1966- 1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Code no.5792: South Central Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Code no.5793: Pacific Telephone Bell of Nevada, Northern California and Nevada Accounting Dept. and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Code no.5794: General Telephone Company of Kentucky and Communications Workers of America, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Code no.5795: Michigan Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Code no.5796: No Employer and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Code no.5799: General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1392, 1972- 1973 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Code no.7982: No Employer and American Federation of Musicians, Phonograph Record Labor Agreement, 1959-1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Code no.7905: United Press International, Inc. and American Newspaper Guild Local 222, Wire Service Guild, 1961-1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Code no.5786: No Employer and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
  - Code no.7417: New York Stock Exchange and Stock Clearing Corporation and Office Employees International Union Local 205, United Financial Employees, 1965-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Code no.7404: Prudential Insurance Company of America and Insurance Workers International Union, 1959-1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Code no.7416: Prudential Insurance Company of America and International Union of Life Insurance Agents, 1965-1972 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Series XV: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
  - Code no.4094: Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division of United Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Lodge 971, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3787: Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. and Communications Workers of America, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Series XVI: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
  - Code no.7406: Building Managers Association of Chicago and Theatre and Amusement Building Janitors' Union Local 25, Chicago Office, 1961-1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Code no.6083: Industrial Refuse Collecting Contractors and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 813, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Code no.7945: Maintenance Contractors and Service and Maintenance Employees' Union, Locals 399, 278, 349, 1963-1976 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Series XVII: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
  - Code no.7939: Metropolitan New York Nursing Home Association, Inc. and Hotel and Allied Service Employees Union Local 144, Hospital and Private Nursing Homes Division, BSEIU, 1963-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Series XVIII: Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
  - Code no.590691: League of Off-Broadway Theatres and Actors' Equity Association, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Code no.591318: Disneyland, Division of Walt Disney Productions and Building and Construction Trades Council of Orange County, 1967- 1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Code no.590494: Several Employers and Service Employees International Union Local 280, Pari-Mutuel Employees Guild of California, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Series XIX: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
  - Code no.7511: Hotel Employers Association of San Francisco and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, San Francisco Local Joint Executive Board, AFL, 1958-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Code no.5717: Pittsburgh Hotels Association, Inc. and Hotel and Restaurant Employees' International Union and Bartenders' International League of America Local 237, Hotel and Restaurant Employees' Alliance, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Code no.7520: Hilton Hawaiian Village Sheraton Hawaii Corporation Waikiki Biltmore and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union Local 5, 1962-1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Code no.7108: Government Services, Inc. and Cafeteria and Restaurant Workers Union, Local 473, 1958-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Code no.7106: Southern Nevada Restaurant and Bar Association, Inc. and Culinary Workers Union Local 226, Local Joint Executive Board of Las Vegas, Nevada, 1958-1965 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Series XX: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
  - Code no.7415: Mount Olivet Cemetery and Cemetery Workers and Greens Attendants Union, Local 365, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Code no.7709: No Employer and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board, 1969- 1972 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Code no.591070: No Employer and Laundry, Dry Cleaning and Dye House Workers International Union, Local 26, 1959-1965 (Box 12, Folder 34)